Hello friends, myself Jagdish Singh from
Hisar, Haryana location
and I have been associated with Lombard for the last 13 years
and my journey
with Lombard is very proud of me in the
sense of claim, in the sense of
services that you
get from the company, whether it is operational
support or claim support, I am in the big
tram industry,
apart from this, if we talk about technology, then the
company is very
concerned with technology and has very advanced
features, if we talk about the training of the company, then the
training part of the company is very good,
such people are associated with flood,
you will do business with flood, your flight has become
very good and very high, thank you
friends
[Music]